mytripjournal.com 2015-03-17

# MyTripJournal - Privacy Policy

| **Privacy Policy**  
---  
**General**  

  * This policy covers how MyTripJournal including its joint venture partners and affiliates and their respective directors, officers, employees and agents (together called "MyTripJournal") treats personal information that it collects and receives in the course of providing goods and services to you relating to MyTripJournal. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. 

  * MyTripJournal will be always be open and honest about the way in which we manage personal information.

 **Collection of Information**  

  * MyTripJournal collects personal information when you subscribe for or other otherwise use MyTripJournal products or services, when you visit MyTripJournal pages or the pages of certain MyTripJournal affiliates, and when you enter any promotions which may be offered.

  * When you subscribe we ask for information such as your name, e-mail address, and country of origin. Once you subscribe to MyTripJournal's products or services, you are not anonymous to us.

  * We may also ask that you provide us with other information such as your address, phone and fax numbers. You are never required to provide this information, but to participate in certain features or to receive certain products, you may be required to provide specific personal information. For example, to receive a MyTripJournal CD you will be required to provide us with your shipping address.

  * MyTripJournal will not collect information which you post on your Personal Travel Website other than the information described in this section. In particular, MyTripJournal will not collect information about your racial or ethnic origin, political views, religious or philosophical beliefs, membership, details about your health, or any other information considered sensitive.

  * MyTripJournal makes limited use of cookies. A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. The cookie helps the user to save time while on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site We do not match cookies to your subscription details and we do not use cookies to track your movements outside of the MyTripJournal System (U.S. patent pending). 

  * MyTripJournal collects information about your transactions with us, including information about your use of financial products and services that we offer. 

  * MyTripJournal automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP (Internet Protocol) address, MyTripJournal cookie information, and the page you request.

  * MyTripJournal monitors traffic patterns and site usage both to our site and to Personal Travel Websites to help us develop the design and layout of the MyTripJournal System, and to provide our users with information relating to access to their Personal Travel Websites (tm).

  * MyTripJournal may share the information which it collects from you with certain of its affiliates, and affiliates related to such affiliates, whose brands are associated from time to time with MyTripJournal products and/or services which we provide to you ("White-Label Affiliates). MyTripJournal may also share the information which it collects from you with Subsequent Service Providers as hereinafter defined for purposes relating to the MyTripJournal service or other collection of online features as operated by MyTripJournal or its respective White-Label Affiliates and/or Subsequent Service Providers. 

**Use of Information and Your Privacy**  

  * MyTripJournal uses information for the following general purposes: to fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide information on our products and services or promotional activities.

  * MyTripJournal, through the MyTripJournal System, currently provides users with rights ("Rights") to access a collection of on-line features as set out herein (the "Service"). Unless explicitly stated otherwise, any new features that augment or enhance the current Service, including the release of new MyTripJournal resources, shall be subject to these terms of service. The Service shall also consist of and include any other collection of on-line features, whether residing on the MyTripJournal.com domain or otherwise and whether similar to the set of features on the MyTripJournal.com domain or not, onto which the Service may be subsequently transitioned, continued and/or exported by MyTripJournal and whether owned by MyTripJournal or by any other persons, individuals, corporations, partnerships, trusts or other entities (each being a "Subsequent Service Provider").

  * We limit access to personal information about you to persons within or related to MyTripJournal who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. All such persons are subject to the same requirements of confidentiality and security as is MyTripJournal.

  * At times MyTripJournal may partner with another party to provide specific services, including credit card processing, and shipment of goods which you have ordered. When you use these services you will provide your name and other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.

  * MyTripJournal will not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with, or permit access to cookies by, other people or companies except under the following circumstances:

  * to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise MyTripJournal's legal rights or defend against legal claims;

  * where we believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of MyTripJournal's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law;

  * to transfer information about you if MyTripJournal or its assets is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, MyTripJournal will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

  * MyTripJournal may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third parties, but these statistics will never include personally identifying information.

 **Your Ability to Edit Your Account Information and Preferences**  

  * You can edit your MyTripJournal account information at any time;

  * You can opt out of receiving future communications on MyTripJournal products or promotional activities or you can unsubscribe by following instructions contained in the messages you receive;

  * We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the MyTripJournal service, such as service announcements, product use advice, administrative messages and newsletters, that are considered part of the service furnished to you by MyTripJournal, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them.

 **Confidentiality and Security**  

  * We limit access to personal information about you to persons within or related to MyTripJournal who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. All such persons are subject to the same requirements of confidentiality and security as is MyTripJournal.

  * At times MyTripJournal may partner with another party to provide specific services, including credit card processing, and shipment of goods which you have ordered. When you use these services you will provide your name and other contact information that is necessary for the third parry to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.

  * Your MyTripJournal account information is password-protected.

  * In certain areas MyTripJournal uses industry-standard encryption technology to protect data transmissions.

  * MyTripJournal will take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we hold about you is protected from misuse and loss or from unauthorized access, modification, or disclosure. MyTripJournal will also take reasonable steps to destroy or de-identify your personal information when we no longer need it.

 **Surveys and Contests**  

  * At times MyTripJournal, its White-Label Affiliates or Subsequent Service Providers, may request information from users through surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), demographic information (such as country of abode, age level), and opinions. Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. If consent is sought and granted, MyTripJournal may publish names of contest winners and their cities or towns of residence to ensure transparency in the contest process and for promotional purposes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of our products and services.

 **Changes to this Privacy Policy**  

  * MyTripJournal may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your MyTripJournal account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.
